BL

CONTACT

25 N State Route 61 Sunbury, OH 43074

bri.loesch@gmail.com 419-544-0998 linkedin.com/in/briloesch

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS

Strategic Communication The Ohio State University

EXPERTISE

CONTENT MANAGEMENT

EMAIL

DIGITAL STRATEGY

ANALYTICS

WRITING/EDITING

SOCIAL MEDIA

GRAPHIC DESIGN

PUBLIC RELATIONS

SKILLS

ADOBE SUITE

HTML

MODX CMS

DRUPAL CMS

BLACKBAUD CRM

BRI LOESCH

PROFILE

I am a communications professional with expertise in email marketing, content management, digital strategy, email and web analytics, html, writing, editing, social media, graphic design and public relations. I excel in a collaborative environment and enjoy staying on top of digital trends. I have experience leading and executing high-level communications projects.

EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL EDITOR | THE OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY

UNIVERSITY MARKETING July 2014-Present

- Responsible for the execution of digital strategy at one of the largest universities in the
 country as part of the interactive communications team. Collaborate most frequently
 with the Alumni Association to create and execute email marketing messages and web
 content for its 500,000 alumni members. Also responsible for sending executive-level
 communications to alumni.
- Lead a community of email editors and other communicators across campus, providing them with training, resources, best practices and recommendations for broadcast email.
- Create and manage content for university websites, utilizing web analytics to inform digital strategies. Currently leading the redesign of Ohio State's visit site, as well a project to consolidate and streamline alumni email efforts to provide a more targeted and engaging experience for constituents.

COMMUNICATIONS COORDINATOR | THE OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY

COLLEGE OF PUBLIC HEALTH June 2012-July 2014

- Produced a wide variety of electronic and written materials aimed to promote and increase recognition of the college. Researched, wrote and edited news stories, feature articles and other content.
- Coordinated production schedule and content for college magazine. Prepared and distributed submissions to strategic news outlets, prepared and distributed e-newsletters, updated web content, created graphics and print materials, produced video content, maintained digital displays and managed college's social networks.

ASSOCIATE EDITOR | THE OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY

COLLEGE OF DENTISTRY
June 2011-June 2012

- Created and managed the college's social media accounts including Twitter, Facebook and LinkedIn.
- Wrote content for the College of Dentistry e-newsletter, website and magazine. Wrote and submitted press releases, edited and proofread promotional and informational communications.
- Provided support for the dean in the form of editing Executive Committee meeting minutes, creating and editing PowerPoint presentations and writing and editing thank you cards.